Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
♪Cannot call back the ones gone♪
♪لا أستطيع استدعاء من رحلوا♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it shatter, let it fade away♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تتحطم، دعها تتلاشى♪
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
♪Endless pain through day and night cycles♪
♪ألم لا ينتهي خلال دورات الليل والنهار♪
♪Longing and care♪
♪الشوق والرعاية♪
=Life Like=
=مثل الحياة=
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
Hey.
يا.
Stop sleeping.
توقف عن النوم
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Go away.
يبتعد.
(Song Residence)
(سكن سونغ)
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I haven't heard from you for so many days.
لم أسمع منك منذ أيام عديدة.
I was worried sick.
لقد كنت قلقا للغاية.
Lucky.
محظوظ.
I'm not dying that easily.
أنا لا أموت بسهولة.
It's fine as long as you're okay.
لا بأس طالما أنك بخير.
Du Hongyue
دو هونغيو
is ruthless.
لا يرحم.
If you're with him,
إذا كنت معه،
you must stay safe.
يجب عليك البقاء آمنًا.
About the students,
عن الطلاب،
did you find anything?
هل وجدت شيئا؟
There's a traitor among the students.
هناك خائن بين الطلاب.
That person secretly sold student info
لقد باع هذا الشخص معلومات الطلاب سرًا
to Song.
الى الأغنية.
Song, to please the Japanese,
أغنية لإرضاء اليابانيين،
secretly captured a batch of students.
أسر مجموعة من الطلاب سراً.
It's been so long,
لقد مر وقت طويل
I still don't know their whereabouts.
ولا أعلم مكانهم حتى الآن.
Those students must be in danger.
لا بد أن هؤلاء الطلاب في خطر.
No. I must get discharged quickly.
لا، يجب أن أخرج بسرعة.
You take care of healing,
أنت تهتم بالشفاء،
I'll personally check Song Residence.
سأقوم شخصياً بالتحقق من Song Residence.
I'll go then.
سأذهب إذن.
I know best
انا اعرف افضل
about those students.
عن هؤلاء الطلاب.
You might
ربما انت
put them in danger.
وضعهم في خطر.
Take care.
يعتني.
Boss, are you okay?
يا رئيس، هل أنت بخير؟
Get out!
اخرج!
If you weren't allowed in, don't come in.
إذا لم يُسمح لك بالدخول، فلا تدخل.
Crazy woman!
امرأة مجنونة!
You dared to trap me!
لقد تجرأت على الإيقاع بي!
(So much like Rose.)
(مثل روز كثيراً.)
Who's there?
من هناك؟
This way!
من هنا!
Yo.
هم.
Musheng.
موشينج.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
I came to find Rose.
لقد جئت للبحث عن روز.
Rose.
وَردَة.
Musheng is here for you.
موشنغ هنا من أجلك.
Oh, okay.
أوه، حسنا.
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
Almost.
بالكاد.
Come, sit.
تعال، اجلس.
This way please.
من هنا من فضلك.
Girls always take their time.
الفتيات يأخذن وقتهن دائمًا.
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
Hurry up.
اسرع.
How many times have I told you?
كم مرة قلت لك؟
Ready.
مستعد.
Every time I have to remind you.
في كل مرة يجب أن أذكرك.
My head's about to explode.
رأسي على وشك الانفجار.
Hey.
يا.
Stubborn girl.
فتاة عنيدة.
Then,
ثم،
you two talk, I'll go first.
تحدثا أنتما الاثنان، سأذهب أولاً.
These past few days,
في الأيام القليلة الماضية،
you didn't come see me.
لم تأت لرؤيتي.
Still angry huh?
لا تزال غاضبا هاه؟
Don't you have your junior?
هل ليس لديك جونيور الخاص بك؟
Why bother with me?
لماذا تهتم بي؟
What did it get stained with?
بماذا تلطخت؟
Looks like blood.
يبدو مثل الدم.
It's lipstick.
إنه أحمر الشفاه.
When I was doing makeup,
عندما كنت أقوم بالمكياج،
it accidentally got on me.
لقد أصابني عن طريق الخطأ.
Doesn't really look like it.
لا يبدو الأمر كذلك حقًا.
Look again now.
أنظر مرة أخرى الآن.
Sweet and lovely.
حلوة وجميلة.
Delicate as silk.
رقيقة كالحرير.
Rose.
وَردَة.
Ready?
مستعد؟
Ready.
مستعد.
I'm coming out.
انا خارج.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
These earrings
هذه الأقراط
really suit you.
تناسبك حقا.
Musheng.
موشينج.
You have great taste.
لديك ذوق رائع.
Master.
يتقن.
Detective Cao.
المحقق كاو.
Please make sure to find the murderer.
من فضلك تأكد من العثور على القاتل.
Give justice to our master.
أعطوا العدل لسيدنا.
Did Mr. Song
هل السيد سونغ
offend anyone before he died?
هل أساء إلى أحد قبل موته؟
I know nothing
لا اعرف شيئا
about the master's affairs outside.
حول شؤون السيد في الخارج.
Who could he have offended?
من كان من الممكن أن يسيء إليه؟
Master.
يتقن.
Red Bean?
الفاصوليا الحمراء؟
♪The world all marvels as fireworks rise♪
♪يندهش العالم كله عندما ترتفع الألعاب النارية♪
♪Magnificent like a blooming dream♪
♪رائعة مثل حلم مزدهر♪
♪Yet who sees the lingering red after the burst♪
♪ومع ذلك من يرى اللون الأحمر المتبقي بعد الانفجار♪
♪Fading into the cold night sky♪
♪تتلاشى في سماء الليل الباردة♪
♪Without the graves of blood and fire♪
♪بدون قبور الدم والنار♪
♪How could there be glory in prosperous times♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مجد في الأوقات المزدهرة♪
♪May that fleeting red of fireworks remain in our hearts♪
♪أتمنى أن يبقى ذلك اللون الأحمر العابر للألعاب النارية في قلوبنا♪
♪Freedom and faith engraved forever♪
♪الحرية والإيمان محفوران إلى الأبد♪
♪You and I are both in the muddy flood♪
♪أنت وأنا في الطوفان الموحل♪
♪Destined to share life and death together♪
♪مُقدَّر لنا أن نتقاسم الحياة والموت معًا♪
♪Life lights the night sky like fireworks' red♪
♪الحياة تضيء سماء الليل مثل الألعاب النارية الحمراء♪
♪Not seeking to engulf the world, just refusing mediocrity♪
♪لا أسعى إلى ابتلاع العالم، فقط أرفض الرداءة♪
♪Even if a single second is all we have in life♪
♪حتى لو كانت ثانية واحدة هي كل ما لدينا في الحياة♪
♪We must sow seeds for our ideals♪
♪علينا أن نزرع بذورًا لمُثُلنا العليا♪